For many it means nothing at all, but to others it is the epitome of their identity.
对很多人来说，头发毫无特殊意义，但对另一些人而言，它却是身份的象征。
As humans, our appearance is often important to us and our hair plays a huge role.
作为人类，我们的外表往往对自己很重要，而头发在其中起着非常关键的作用。
Whether you have long flowing locks or a swept-back do, the way you wear your hair can say something about you.
无论你留着飘逸的长发，还是大背头，发型都能透露出你的一些特质。
But what if you start to lose it?
但如果你开始脱发了怎么办？
Forty per cent of men experience hair loss by the age of 35, according to the Belgravia Centre UK, one of Europe's largest hair loss treatment centres. This figure rises to 80% by the age of 80.
英国贝尔格拉维亚中心是欧洲最大的脱发治疗中心之一，该中心表示，40%的男性在35岁前会经历脱发，到80岁时这一比例会升至80%。
And women are far from exempt from losing clumps of hair, with 50% of them suffering some form of hair loss in their life.
女性也绝不能幸免脱发问题，50%的女性在一生中会遭受某种形式的脱发困扰。
It starts with a receding hairline, followed by a thinning of hair on the crown of the head and temples and before you know it, your scalp is showing and you're completely bald.
脱发通常始于发际线后移，随后头顶和太阳穴部位的头发逐渐变稀疏，不知不觉中头皮就会显露出来，最终完全秃顶。
Every human naturally loses between 50 and 100 hairs a day, according to the UK National Health Service.
英国国家医疗服务体系称，每个人每天都会自然脱落50至100根头发。
Excluding hair loss caused by disease, baldness is genetic.
排除疾病导致的脱发，秃顶大多与遗传有关。
It's related to the hormone testosterone, which causes a shrinking of hair follicles in susceptible adults. This results in the loss of so called 'terminal' adult hair and the production of much finer 'vellus' hairs – like those on the heads of babies.
它与荷尔蒙睾酮相关，这种激素会导致易感成年人的毛囊萎缩，进而导致所谓的“终毛”（成人成熟毛发）脱落，并长出更纤细的“绒毛”——类似婴儿头上的毛发。
'It can cause considerable damage to emotional health, including loss of self-esteem and confidence.' a spokesman for the British Association of Dermatologists told the BBC.
英国皮肤科医师协会的发言人告诉英国广播公司：“脱发会对心理健康造成相当大的损害，包括丧失自尊和自信。”
But if you can't hide it with a comb-over, or a wig, what can you do?
但如果无法用梳发遮盖或戴假发掩饰，你还能怎么办？
Well, the ancient Greek medic Hippocrates recommended a mixture of pigeon droppings, mixed with horseradish, cumin and nettles liberally applied to the pate.
古希腊医生希波克拉底曾建议，将鸽子粪便与辣根、孜然和荨麻混合，大量涂抹在头顶。
Since then, there has been a huge range of tonics, creams, pills and hair replacement surgery. All of which have had mixed results.
从那以后，市面上出现了各种各样的滋补液、乳膏、药片和植发手术，但效果参差不齐。
Now, a potential new cure has been found in a drug that was designed to treat osteoporosis.
如今，一种原本用于治疗骨质疏松症的药物被发现可能成为新的脱发疗法。
The research, published in PLOS Biology, states that the drug contains a compound that targets a protein which inhibits hair growth and plays a role in balding. In short, it stimulates hair to grow.
发表在《公共科学图书馆·生物学》（PLOS Biology）上的研究表明，这种药物含有一种化合物，能够针对抑制头发生长并参与脱发过程的蛋白质发挥作用。
Keep your hair on, though.
简而言之，它能刺激头发生长。
Clinical trials need to take place to ensure the drug is effective and safe to give to people.
不过请保持冷静，还需要进行临床试验，以确保这种药物对人体有效且安全。
And besides, many would say that being bald improves a person's appearance.
此外，很多人认为秃顶会让人更有魅力。
Researchers at The University of Pennsylvania asked male and female students to rate photographs of men according to their attractiveness, confidence and dominance.
宾夕法尼亚大学的研究人员让男女学生根据吸引力、自信心和支配力三个维度，对男性照片进行评分。
In all three categories, the bald men came out ahead - and not just by a hair's breadth.
结果显示，秃顶男性在这三个维度上都名列前茅——而且优势明显。
So, whether you love it or hate it or whether it's happening to you right now, you aren't alone.
所以，无论你喜欢还是讨厌秃顶，无论你现在是否正经历脱发，你都不是一个人。
A cure may very soon be on its way.
治愈脱发的方法可能很快就会出现。
Until then, relax and let your hair down.
在那之前，放松心情，别太紧张啦。